videocollector.co.uk 2019-04-15

# VideoCollector.co.uk Privacy Policy

**1 Protecting Your Privacy**

VideoCollector.co.uk is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UK. The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.

**2 Ordering Details**

When you order, we need to know your name, address, email address and card details (we do not store or process card details). This allows us to process and fulfil your order. You have the option to withhold personal information that is not required for the order process.

**3 How We Use Your Personal Information**

We use your personal information to update you about new products/services. We will only contact you with your consent.

**4 What We Don't Do**

We do not sell, rent or exchange your personal information with any third party for commercial reasons, beyond the essential requirement for credit/debit card validation during purchase.

**5 Security**

We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access in accordance with the UK data protection legislation.

We do not collect sensitive information about you except when you specifically knowingly provide it. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details by [contacting us](http://www.videocollector.co.uk/contact.php).

**6 Any Questions?**

If you have any questions about privacy please [contact us](http://www.videocollector.co.uk/contact.php).

**7 Third Party Advertising**

We use third party advertisements on VideoCollector.co.uk to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

<http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>

* * *

• Read our [Privacy Policy](http://www.videocollector.co.uk/privacy.php "VideoCollector.co.uk Privacy Policy") • Your access to and use of this Website is conditional on your acceptance of these [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.videocollector.co.uk/terms-of-use.php "Terms and Conditions of Use of the website") © VideoCollector.co.uk 2019 Overseas
